weddingtonway.com 2017-04-06

# Privacy Policy | Weddington Way

Weddington Way Privacy Policy 

This Privacy Policy applies to Weddington Way. Weddington Way is a member of the Gap Inc. family of companies. For details on how Gap Inc. and its brands may collect, use and share your personal information please see the [privacy policy for Gap Inc.](http://www.gapinc.com/content/gapinc/html/toolbar/privacypolicy.html)

Effective Date: March 17, 2017

We at Weddington Way ("Weddington Way," "we," "us," "our") know that our users ("you," "your") care about how your personal information is used and shared, and we take your privacy seriously. Please read the following to learn more about our Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy applies to data collected through the Weddingtonway.com website, the Weddington Way mobile app and your interactions with Weddington Way's services. **By visiting or using the WeddingtonWay.com website and domain name, and any other linked pages, features, content, or any other services we offer from time to time by in connection therewith (collectively, the “Website”), you acknowledge that you accept the practices and policies outlined in this Privacy Policy, and you hereby consent that we will collect, use, and share your information in the following ways.**

I. What Does This Privacy Policy Cover? 

This Privacy Policy covers our treatment of personally identifiable information (“Personal Information”) that we gather when you are accessing or using our Website. This policy does not apply to the practices of companies that we do not own or control, or to individuals that we do not employ or manage. ****

We do not knowingly collect or solicit Personal Information from anyone under the age of 13 or knowingly allow such persons to register. If you are under 13, please do not attempt to register for the Website or send any information about yourself to us, including your name, address, telephone number, or email address. No one under age 13 may provide any personal information to us or on the Website. In the event that we learn that we have collected personal information from a child under age 13 without verification of parental consent, we will delete that information as quickly as possible. If you believe that we might have any information from or about a child under 13, please contact us at legal@weddingtonway.com. 

II. What Information Does Weddington Way Collect? 

We gather various types of Personal Information from our users, as explained more fully below. We may use this Personal Information to personalize and improve our services, to allow our users to set up a user account and profile, to contact users, to fulfill your requests for certain products and services, to analyze how users utilize the Website, and as otherwise set forth in this Privacy Policy. We may share certain types of Personal Information with third parties (as set forth in this Section and in Section III below). We collect the following types of information: 

**A. Information You Provide to Us:**

We receive and store any information you knowingly provide to us. For example, during the registration process, we may collect Personal Information such as your name, user name, email address, mobile phone number, IP address, browser information, credit card information, the date of your wedding or the wedding you're a part of ("Event Date") and third-party account credentials (for example, your log-in credentials for Facebook or other third party sites). If you provide your third-party account credentials to us, you understand some content and/or information in those accounts ("Third Party Account Information"), such as your third party account profile picture, may be transmitted into your account with us, and that Third Party Account Information transmitted to our Website is covered by this Privacy Policy. We may collect other Personal Information you provide us through your use of our services, including without limitation your dress size, measurements, and preferences regarding certain dresses. You can choose not to provide us with certain information, but then you may not be able to take advantage of many of our special features. An email address is required to register with us. 

**B. Information Collected Automatically:**

Whenever you interact with our Website, we automatically receive and record information on our server logs from your browser including your IP address, "cookie" information, and the page you requested. "Cookies" are identifiers we transfer to your computer or mobile device that allow us to recognize your browser and tell us how and when pages in our site are visited and by how many people. You may be able to change the preferences on your browser to prevent or limit your computer or other device's acceptance of cookies, but this may prevent you from taking advantage of some of our Website's best features. Our advertising partners may also transmit cookies to your computer, when you click on ads that appear on our Website. Also, if you click on a link to a third party website, such third party may also transmit cookies to you. Again, this Privacy Policy does not cover the use of cookies by any third parties, and we aren't responsible for their privacy policies and practices. Please be aware that cookies placed by third parties may continue to track your activities online even after you have left our Services, and those third parties may not honor "Do Not Track" requests you have set using your browser or device. 

We also collect usage information, including without limitation the numbers and frequency of visitors to our Website. We only use this data in aggregate form, and not in a manner that would identify you personally. For example, this aggregate data tells us how often customers use parts of the Website, so that we can make the Website appealing to as many customers as possible. We may also provide this aggregate information to our partners, so that they can understand how often and in what ways people use their services and our Website, so that they, too, can provide you with an optimal experience. We never disclose aggregate information to a partner in a manner that would identify you personally. 

Through cookies we place on your browser or device, we may collect usage information about your online activity after you leave our Services. Just like any other usage information we collect, this information allows us to improve the Services and customize your online experience, and otherwise as described in this Privacy Policy. Your browser may offer you a "Do Not Track" option, which allows you to signal to operators of websites and web applications and services (including without limitation the numbers and frequency of behavioral advertising services) that you do not wish such operators to track certain of your online activities over time and across different websites. Our Services do not support Do Not Track requests at this time, which means that we collect information about your online activity both while you are using the Services and after you leave our Services. 

**C. E-mail and Other Communications:**

We may contact you, by email or other means; for example, we may send you promotional offers on behalf of other businesses, or communicate with you about your use of the Website. If you have provided us with your mobile phone number, we may contact you via text message to let you know the status of your order (please be aware that standard messaging rates will apply). If you do not want to receive email or other communications from us, please contact us at stylists@weddingtonway.com. Also, we may receive a confirmation when you open an email from us. This confirmation helps us make emails more interesting and improve our service. 

**III. Will Weddington Way Share Any Of The Personal Information It Receives?**

We share your Personal Information in personally identifiable form with third parties only as described below. 

**A. Online Advertising Networks:** We may allow advertisers to choose the demographic information of users who will see their advertisements and we may provide information we have collected from you to an advertiser in non-personally-identifiable form, in order for that advertiser to select the appropriate audience for its advertisements. For example, we might use your interest in a certain brand of bridesmaid dress to show you ads for the company that sells that brand, but we do not tell that company who you are. 

We may deliver a file to you through the Website (known as a "web beacon") from an ad network. Web beacons allow ad networks to provide anonymized, aggregated auditing, research, and reporting for us and for advertisers. Web beacons also enable ad networks to serve targeted advertisements to you when you visit other websites. Because your web brower must request these advertisements and web beacons from the ad network's servers, these companies can view, edit, or set their own cookies, just as if you had requested a web page from their site. 

**B. Affiliated Businesses and Third Party Services We Do Not Control:** In certain situations, businesses or third party services we're affiliated with may sell items or provide services to you through the Website (either alone or jointly with us). You can recognize when an affiliated business is associated with such a transaction or service, and we will share your Personal Information with that affiliated business only to the extent that it is related to such transaction or service. One such service may include the ability for you to choose to automatically transmit Third Party Account Information to your Website profile or to automatically transmit information in your Website profile to your third party account. 

**C. Non-Affiliated Companies or Promotional Partners** Additionally, like other retailers, we may establish a business relationship with other persons,  companies or organizations who are not part of Weddington Way or the Gap Inc. family of companies, but are offering a product or service that you may find useful or enjoyable (“Promotional Partners”).   We may share information we have collected, including your personal information, with our Promotional Partners for their use in providing you with information about their products or services. **If you do not want us to share your information with our Promotional Partners, please email us at legal@weddingtonway.com to opt out.** Please note that we have no control over the policies and practices of third party websites or businesses as to privacy or anything else, so if you choose to take part in any transaction or service relating to an affiliated website or business, please review all such businesses' or third party websites' policies and privacy statements. After your information has been shared with a Promotional Partner, you will need to opt-out of their communications by contacting the Promotional Partner directly. For details on how to opt-out, see our Promotional Partners' privacy statements and/or promotional materials and communications. 

**D. Agents:** We employ other companies and people to perform tasks on our behalf and need to share your information with them to provide products or services to you. Unless we tell you differently, our agents do not have any right to use the Personal Information we share with them beyond what is necessary to assist us. For example, if you were to engage in a credit card transaction via the Website, we would need to allow a credit card processing company to verify the transaction; however, that company would only be authorized to use your credit card information to the extent we needed their assistance in completing your transaction. 

**E. User Profiles and Submissions:** __ Certain user profile information, including without limitation a user's name, email address, user name, photo, Event Date, and preferences regarding certain dresses, may be displayed to other users to facilitate user interaction within the Website or address your request for Company's services. Your account privacy settings allow you to limit the other users who can see the Personal Information in your user profile and/or what information in your user profile is visible to others. When you submit or provide certain types of User Submissions in connection with our Website and services, they are considered "Public-Use User Submissions," and become publicly available (and/or in sharing them, you are permitting Weddington Way to make them publicly available), and can be collected and used by anyone (including by us in our promotional materials), so please keep this in mind whenever you share a Public-Use User Submission. "Public-Use User Submissions" means (i) photos and text regarding your event and your experience with our dresses that you submit to us via email, excluding requests for support or other concerns regarding the services, (ii) any content you upload to your public user profile, and (iii) any content that you voluntarily disclose online in a manner other users can view, including on discussion boards, in messages and chat areas, and, as part of a product review. Your user name may be displayed to other users if and when you send messages or comments or upload images through the Website and other users can contact you through messages and comments. 

**E. Business Transfers:** We may share your personal information within the Gap Inc. group of affiliated companies and brands. We may choose to buy or sell assets. In these types of transactions, customer information is typically one of the business assets that is transferred. Also, if we (or substantially all of our assets) are acquired, or if we are reorganized or go through some other change of control (including without limitation going into bankruptcy), Personal Information would be one of the assets transferred to or acquired by a third party. 

**F. Protection of Weddington Way and Others:** We reserve the right to access, read, preserve, and disclose any information that we reasonably believe is necessary to comply with laws; enforce or apply our conditions of use and other agreements; or protect the rights, property, or safety of Weddington Way, our employees, our users, or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations for fraud protection and credit risk reduction. 

IV. Is Personal Information About Me Secure? 

Your account is protected by a password for your privacy and security. You need to prevent unauthorized access to your account and Personal Information by selecting and protecting your password appropriately and limiting access to your computer or device and browser by signing off after you have finished accessing your account. 

We endeavor to protect the privacy of your account and other Personal Information we hold in our records, but we cannot guarantee complete security. Unauthorized entry or use, hardware or software failure, and other factors may compromise the security of user information at any time. 

The Website may contain links to other sites. We are not responsible for the privacy policies and/or practices on other sites. When following a link to another site you should read that site's privacy policy. 

V. what personal information can i access? 

Through your account settings, you may access and, in some cases, change or delete the following information you've provided to us: 

  * Username and password
  * Email address
  * User profile information
  * Credit card and payment information
  * Mobile phone number
  * Shipping address

The information you can view and update may change as the Website changes. If you have any questions about viewing or updating information we have on file about you, please contact us at support@weddingtonway.com. Under California Civil Code Sections 1798.83-1798.84, California residents are entitled to ask us for a notice identifying the categories of Personal Information which we share with our affiliates and/or third parties for marketing purposes, and providing contact information for such affiliates and/or third parties. If you are a California resident and would like a copy of this notice, please submit a written request to support@weddingtonway.com. 

VI. What Choices Do I Have? 

  * You can always opt not to disclose information to us, but keep in mind some information may be needed to take advantage of some of our special features. An email address is required in order to register with us. 
  * You may be able to add, update, or delete certain information as explained in Section V above. When you update information, however, we may maintain a copy of the unrevised information in our records. Please note that some information may remain in our records after your deletion of such information from your account. We may use any aggregated data derived from or incorporating your Personal Information after you update or delete your information, but not in a manner that would identify you personally. 
  * If you do not wish to receive email or other mail from us, please contact us at unsubscribe@weddingtonway.com. Please note that if you do not want to receive legal notices from us via email, such as this Privacy Policy, those legal notices will still govern your use of the Website, and you are responsible for reviewing such legal notices for changes. 

VII. Changes to this Privacy Policy 

We may amend this Privacy Policy from time to time. Use of information we collect now is subject to the Privacy Policy in effect at the time such information is collected. If we make changes in the way we use Personal Information, we will notify you by posting an announcement on our Website or sending you an email. You are bound by any changes to the Privacy Policy when you use the Website after such changes have been first posted. 

VIII. Questions or Concerns 

If you have any questions or concerns regarding our privacy policies, please send us a detailed message to support@weddingtonway.com. We will make every effort to resolve your concerns.
